"迷失" 前情提要...
Previously on "Lost"...
我们现在准备降落在
We're now beginning our final descent
洛杉矶国际机场
into Los Angeles International Airport.
Shephard先生 你托运的
Mr. Shephard, there seems to have been a mix-up
- 呃 棺材 好像出了点问题  - 他们把我爸弄丢了
- involving the, uh, coffin.  - They lost my father.
他几天前在澳大利亚过世
He died in Australia a couple days ago.
- 你是谁?  - Jacob让我们来的 他说你能帮助我们的朋友
- Who are you?  - Jacob sent us. He said you would help our friend.
送他去泉水那里
Get him to the spring.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
他说 你得把这粒药给你朋友
He says you have to give your friend this pill.
- 这里面是什么?  - 毒药
- What is in it?  - Poison.
- 你们为什么想杀Sayid?  - 啊!
- Why would you people wanna kill Sayid?  - Aah!
他体内有股暗黑势力 正在滋长
There is a darkness growing in him.
你怎么知道的?
How can you be sure of that?
因为 此事曾在你妹妹身上发生过
Because it happened to your sister.
啊! 啊!
Aah! Uhh!
你是Claire?
Claire?
嘿 妈妈
Hey, mom.
找到他了吗?
Have they found him yet?
没 我... 我几小时前打电话问过
No, I... I called a couple hours ago,
他们说棺材在柏林过了安检
and they think the coffin was checked through Berlin.
你怎么会把遗体搞丢呢?
How do you lose a body?
我不知道 妈妈 但我们无能为力
I don't know, mom, but there's nothing we can do
- 只能继续等消息  - 我等不下去 Jack
- except for wait for more information.  - I don't want to wait, Jack.
这叫我怎么去完成葬礼?
How am I supposed to get anything done?
我甚至连他的遗嘱都找不到 到处都是纸
I can't even find his will. Papers everywhere.
听我说 妈妈 我几小时后就到家了
Look, mom, I'll come over in a couple hours,
然后我们一起找 好吗?
And we'll find it together. Okay?
好吧
Okay.
好 还有 妈妈 我的阑尾是什么时候切除的?
Good. Now, mom, when did I have my appendix taken out?
大概在你七八岁的时候吧
You were 7 or 8 maybe.
你上学的时候痛晕了过去
You collapsed at school.
你爸本来想自己主刀的
Your father wanted to do the procedure himself,
但他们不让 你不记得这事了么?
but they wouldn't let him. You don't remember that?
不 我...
Yeah, I...
我想我记得的
I guess I do.
哦 要命 妈妈 我得走了
Oh, damn it. Mom, I gotta go.
哦 别忘了...
Well, don't forget to...
嘿
Hey.
抱歉 我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
我以为 下班后我有足够的时间回家 并换身衣服
I thought I had enough time to go home and change after work.
没关系
Don't worry about it.
抱歉 David 别生气 好么?
I'm sorry, David. Okay?
没事的 爸爸
Okay, dad.
我怕你走了
I was afraid you'd left.
我有选择离开的权力吗?
Is leaving an option?
凡事皆有选择
Everything is an option.
但我会阻止你的
But I would have to stop you.
嗯 我就欣赏你的坦诚
Well, I appreciate your honesty.
你的朋友... Ford和Austen 还有Kwon...
Your friends... Ford and Austen and Kwon...
他们不回来了 对吗?
They're not coming back, are they?
是啊 可能不回来了
No, probably not.
我也很欣赏你的坦诚
I appreciate your honesty.
又打平了 老兄
Tie again, dude.
- 真让我吃惊  - 这话该我来说
- Shocker.  - That's it for me.
你饿了吗?
You hungry?
你饿了?
Are you?
我想吃东西
I could eat.
嘿 伙计
Hey, man.
你知道这里 有类似于厨房的地方吗?
Do you know if there's, like, a kitchen in this place?
走道过去就是 Hugo
It's all the way down the hallway, Hugo.
老兄 你在这儿干嘛?
Dude, what are you doing here?
我是来找你的
I'm here because I need you.
找我干嘛?
For what?
你得弄支笔来
You should probably get a pen.
然后记点儿东西
You're gonna have to write a few things down.
- 记什么?  - 有人要来岛上了
- What kind of things?  - Someone is coming to the island.
我要你帮他们找到他
I need you to help them find it.
把线接上
Hooked up the cable in here
你想看"红袜"队比赛的时候 就可以看了
so you can watch the Red Sox if you want.
谢谢
Thanks.
你在看这本书?
You reading this?
嗯
Yeah.
你小时候 我经常念这给你听
I used to read this to you when you were little.
你总想知道Kitty和Snowdrop的事
You always wanted to hear about Kitty and Snowdrop.
他们是爱丽丝的...
They were Alice's...
嘿
Hey.
嘿!
Hey!
David啊
David.
你在听什么?
What are you listening to?
说了你也不知道
You haven't heard of them.
我想跟你谈谈 David
I'm just trying to have a conversation with you, David.
干嘛?
Why?
我们大概 呃 一个月才见一次面 就不能...
We see each other, like, once a month. Can't we just...
消停一下?
get through it?
真要命
Damn it.
喂 妈妈?
Yeah, mom?
你在哪? 我以为你过来了
Where are you? I thought you were coming over.
嗯 抱歉 呃 我马上出门
Yeah, I'm sorry. Um, I'm heading out right now.
- 很快就到  - 好吧
- I'll be right there.  - Okay.
我得去你奶奶家一趟
I have to go over to your grandmother's house.
- 你要一起去吗?  - 不 谢谢
- You wanna come?  - No, thanks.
好吧 呃 我一个钟头左右就回来
All right, well, I'll be back in about an hour.
然后我们一起吃饭 好吗?
And then we'll eat, okay?
好的
Great.
Jack啊
Jack.
是Sayid啊
Sayid.
他们干嘛盯着我看?
Why are they all staring at me?
别理他们就是
Just ignore them.
呃 你跟我说过 这些人以为我得了传染病
Look, you told me these people think I have an infection,
他们想给我吃奇怪的药
that they wanted to give me some mysterious pill
你却告诫我不要吃
that you instructed me not to take.
接着你又消失了
And then you disappeared.
你在瞒着我什么?
What are you hiding from me?
那药是毒药
The pill was poison.
他们想借我的手杀了你
They wanted me to kill you.
甭管他们以为你怎么了 Sayid...
Whatever it is they think happened to you, Sayid...
他们说 这事以前在某人身上也发生过
They say it happened to someone else, too.
谁?
Who?
Claire啊!
Claire!
我来撬开它
I'm gonna get you out of there.
你在这儿待了多久?
How long have you been out here?
从你们走后起
Since you all left.
那是多久前的事?
How long ago was that?
是三年前
Three years.
我带你去个安全的地方 快点 你可以自己走吗?
I gotta get you somewhere safe. Come on. You think you can walk?
我也不知道
I don't know.
啊! 呃!
Aah! Uhh!
啊! 好了 好了 可以了
Aah! Okay. Okay. Okay.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
没干嘛
Nothin'.
不过就是... 看看...
I'm just... you know, looking...
因为我超爱寺庙啊
'cause I'm a big fan of temples
像历史啊...
and, like, history...
还有像"夺宝奇兵"里那些东西
and Indiana Jones stuff.
你不该来这儿
You shouldn't be here.
回院子里去
Go back to the courtyard.
告诉他 你想怎样就怎样
Tell him you can do what you want.
告诉他 你是接班人
Tell him you're a candidate.
我是接班人 我想怎样就怎样
I'm a candidate, and I can do what I want.
谁告诉你的?
Who told you that?
这不重要
Doesn't matter.
你何不回院子里去呢?
Why don't you go back to the courtyard?
他说了什么?
What'd he say?
你不会想知道的 你在这儿干嘛 Hugo?
You don't want to know. What are you doing here, Hugo?
正想穿过这条秘道
Going through the secret passageway
- 是你叫我这么做的  - 我叫你带上Jack
- like you told me.  - I told you to bring Jack with you.
你试过让Jack去做什么事吗? 这根本不可能嘛
You ever tried to get Jack to do something? It's, like, impossible.
- 我可以一个人去  - 你必须把他带上 Hugo
- I can just go myself.  - You have to bring him with you, Hugo.
好吧 你让我记下这么多东西 已经够糟糕的了
Okay, it's bad enough you already made me write down
我刚刚还对一个日本武士撒了谎
way too much stuff, and I just lied to a samurai.
听着 要是你有什么主意 能让Jack
Look, if you have any idea on how to get Jack
去干你的小探险 那就说啊 老兄
to go on your little adventure, I'm listening, dude.
保持镇定 伙计
Be cool, man.
表现得自然点
Act natural.
什么?
What?
老兄 声音小点
Dude, keep your voice down.
我等下会站起来 离开
I'm gonna get up and go.
十秒之后 跟上我
Wait ten seconds and then follow me.
跟着你去哪儿?
Follow you where?
我找到了一条通往丛林的秘道
I found a secret tunnel that leads out to the jungle.
你找到一条秘道?
You found a secret tunnel?
嗯... 是Jacob告诉我的
Well... Jacob told me about it.
- 他说我们俩得去...  - 我哪儿都不去 Hurley
- He said you and me have to go...  - I'm not going anywhere, Hurley.
我告诉过他 你肯定会这么说的 所以他叫我告诉你...
I told him you'd say that, so he told me to tell you...
你身上有玄机
You have what it takes.
你刚刚说什么?
What did you just say?
我说 "你身上有玄机"
I said, "you have what it takes,"
他说 你知道这是什么意思
He said you'd know what that meant.
- 他在哪儿?  - 什么?
- Where is he?  - What?
Jacob 他在哪儿?
Jacob. Where is he?
他相当于死人一个
He's kind of dead.
他想出现时就会出现 就像Obi-Wan Kenobi("星际大战"中的绝地武士)
He turns up whenever he wants, like Obi-Wan Kenobi.
不过如果你想跟他谈谈 他就在我们要去的地方 老兄
But if you wanna talk to him, he's where we're going, dude.
好吧 那我们去找Jacob
Well, then let's go see Jacob.
Claire啊?
Claire?
好了 看我抓到了谁... 是其中一个想杀你的人
Well, look what I found... one of the men who tried to kill you.
他只是装死 实际上根本没死
He was just pretending to be dead, but he wasn't.
现在我们得和他谈谈
Now we get to talk to him.
你想和我谈什么?
You wanna talk to me about what?
谈谈你们把我儿子藏哪儿了
About where you're hiding my son.
得帮你清洗干净
Gotta get that cleaned up.
如果说在这儿 有什么能要你的命的话
If there's one thing that'll kill you around here,
那就是感染了
it's infection.
我马上回来 别乱走动 好吗?
I'll be right back. Don't move, okay?
Claire啊?
Claire?
你一直在这儿... 就你一个人吗?
Have you been out here all this time... by yourself?
哦 我... 我不是一个人
Oh, I'm... I'm not by myself.
听着 我们得马上离开这儿
Look, we've gotta get out of here now.
没事的 我了解她
It's okay. I know her.
不 我才了解她
No, I know her.
你不知道她要怎么对我们吗?
You have any idea what she's gonna do to us?
如果我们不马上离开 她会把我们俩都杀了
If we don't get out of here now, she's gonna kill us both.
走哪边?
Which way?
走这边
It's this way.
哇! 嘿!
Whoa! Hey!
是我
It's me.
是Jack!
Jack!
我差点开了枪
I almost shot you.
我注意到了 你在这儿干嘛?
I noticed. What are you doing out here?
呃 Jin和Sawyer人呢?
Where's, uh, where's Jin and Sawyer?
Jin回寺庙去了 嗯...
Jin went back to the temple, and, um...
Sawyer独自走了
Sawyer's on his own.
嘿 Kate 有一个暗门可以回寺庙
Hey, Kate, there's a secret door to get back in the temple,
就在大树后的北墙上
on the north wall behind the big tree.
嗯 我不准备回寺庙
Yeah, I'm not going back to the temple.
我要去找Claire
I'm going to find Claire.
- Kate...  - 我准备回海滩营地
- Kate...  - I'm going back to the beach camp.
- 她也许还在那儿 Jack  - Kate 她不在海滩那儿
- She might still be there, Jack.  - Kate, she's not up at the beach.
寺庙那儿的人说她...
The people at the temple said that something...
她出了点事
something happened to her.
- 他们知道她在哪儿吗?  - 我不知道 他们没说
- Do they know where she is?  - I don't know. They didn't say.
我... 我得找到她
I... I have to find her.
Kate 等会儿 等会儿
Kate, wait. Wait.
跟我们一起 然后我们一起回寺庙
Come with us, and then we'll all go back to the temple together.
老兄 Jacob说了只有我和你
Dude, Jacob said just you and me.
没邀请她
She's kinda not invited.
我正邀请她呢
I'm inviting her.
Jack 没事 去吧 没关系
Jack, it's okay. Just go. It's all right.
我希望 你能找到你想找的东西
I hope you find what you're looking for.
我们永远找不到了
We're never going to find it.
别激动 妈
Take it easy, Mom.
他就在这儿的某个地方 我们会找到的
It's somewhere in here, and we'll find it.
简直就是大海捞针
It's like a needle in a damned haystack.
你爸干嘛不直接把遗嘱给律师
Why your father wouldn't just give his will to his lawyer
如果他不想给我的话?
he's beyond me?
好了... 他干嘛要让我们这时候 无所事事呢?
Well... Why would he make it easier on us now?
想喝杯酒吗?
You want a drink?
呃 不了 谢谢
Uh, no. No, no thanks.
你能这样就好
Good for you.
David恢复得还好吗?
How's David holding up?
什么?
What?
葬礼上他非常不安
He was really upset at the funeral.
是吗?
He was?
他没告诉你?
He didn't tell you?
不 不 他没有
No. No, he didn't.
他不善于交流
Communication is not one of his strong suits.
嗯 遗传你的性格
Well, it runs in the family.
你像David那么大时
When you were David's age,
你要是
your father was lucky
能多跟你爸爸说一句话 就很难得了
if he could get more than one word out of you at a time.
嗯 那是因为我害怕他 妈妈
that's because I was terrified of him, mom.
那你怎么知道 David就不怕你呢?
How do you know David isn't terrified of you?
他为什么要怕我?
Why would he be?
我不知道 Jack
I don't know, Jack.
也许 你该亲自问问他
Maybe you should ask him.
找到了
Found it.
"临终遗嘱"
"Last will and testament."
Jack啊?
Jack?
嗯?
Yeah?
你父亲曾经提到过
Did you father ever mention
一个... 叫Claire Littleton的人吗?
a... Claire Littleton?
喂 嘿
Ow psst. Hey.
在她回来之前 快帮我松绑
Untie me before she comes back in.
我为什么要这么做?
Why would I do that?
你没听到我的话吗? 她会把我们俩都杀死的
Are you not listening to me? She's gonna kill us both.
给我把绳子解开 然后 她一进来
Loosen my ropes, and when she comes back in,
我就掐断她的脖子
I'll snap her neck.
嗯...
So...
我 呃 很抱歉 我布下的陷阱伤了你
I'm, uh, really sorry you got stuck in my trap.
现在 我要帮你清洗一下 好吗?
Gonna get you all cleaned up now, okay?
很好 你做得很好
It's all right. You're doing good.
嗯 至少 你不用亲自缝合伤口
Well, at least you don't have to stitch yourself up.
我曾经自己缝过一次 他们打中了我这里
I did that once. They shot me right here.
我们走后 你就一直住在这儿?
You've been living here since we left?
不是一直在这儿
Not always here.
我 呃 为了躲避他们 不得不时常转移
I, um, had to move around quite a lot to hide from them.
很幸运 我还没死
Lucky I'm still alive.
你要把他怎么样?
What are you gonna do with him?
我要他告诉我 他们把我的孩子弄到哪儿去了...
He's gonna tell me where they've got my baby...
在哪... 我儿子Aron在哪
Where... Where they've got Aron.
我们没抓你儿子
We don't have your kid.
你说谎 嗯? 我知道你们抓了他
You're lying, okay? I know you have him.
这太荒谬了 我们从来没有抓走你的...
That's crazy. We never took your...
- 闭嘴  - Claire 你怎么知道是他们干的?
- Shut up.  - Claire, how do you know they took him?
- 你怎么能如此确定?  - 我怎么能确定?
- How can you be so sure?  - How can I be so sure?
好 嗯 首先 是我父亲告诉我的
Okay, well, first my father told me,
然后是我的朋友 所以 我非常确定
and then my friend told me, so I'm pretty damn sure.
你的朋友? 你的朋友是谁?
Your friend? Who is your friend?
就是我的朋友
My friend.
你依然是我的朋友 对吧 Jin?
You're still my friend, aren't you, Jin?
对
Yes.
是 当然是
Yes, of course.
很好
Good.
我很高兴
I'm glad.
好了 恢复如初
All done. Good as new.
好
Okay.
那么...
So...
现在 轮到你了
Now it's your turn.
对不起 老兄
Sorry, dude.
为什么?
For what?
嗯 为了以前这里发生的事
You know, what happened back there,
你和Kate的分手
wrecking your game with kate.
没关系
Don't worry about it.
现在已经没有什么 可失去的了
There's nothing left to wreck.
是吗? 你们之间到底发生了什么?
Yeah? Whatever happened to you guys?
我本以为你们会
I thought you guys were gonna get married
结婚生子
and have, like, a dozen kids.
我想我不是那块料
Guess I wasn't cut out for it.
是吗? 我觉得你会是个好父亲
Really? I think you'd make a great dad.
我会是一个非常糟糕的父亲
I'd make a terrible dad.
那是什么?
What is that?
哮喘吸入器
Asthma inhaler.
老兄 那是Shannon的
Dude, it's Shannon's.
我们在洞穴这儿
We're at the caves.
我们住过的那个洞穴?
The caves we used to live in?
我差点忘了这儿有这些东西 伙计
I totally forgot these were in here, man.
等等
Wait a sec.
假如我们又经历了一次时空穿梭
What if we time traveled again
嗯 去到了 恐龙时代
to, like, dinosaur times,
然后我们死了 接着被埋葬在了这儿 那会怎样?
and then we died and then we got buried here?
假如这些骷髅 就是我们自己呢?
What if these skeletons are us?
那是什么?
What's that?
我告诉过你 我是怎么找到这个地方的吗?
I ever tell you how I found this place?
你那时正在找水源 对吧?
You were looking for water, right?
不
No.
我在追赶我父亲的幽灵
I was chasing the ghost of my dead father.
是他把我带到了这儿
He led me here.
那是他的棺材...
That was his coffin...
后来我把它砸了
Before I smashed it to pieces.
你为什么要那么做?
Why'd you do that?
因为里面是空的
Because he wasn't in it.
David啊?
David?
我买了匹萨
I got us a pizza.
嘿 晚饭...
Hey, dinner's...
我是David 请留言
This is David. Leave a message.
David 是... 还是我
David, it... it's me again.
听着 嗯...
Listen, uh...
如果我真的 做了什么让你不安的事
If I did something to upset you,
我真的 真的很抱歉
I am really, really sorry.
嗯 我现在马上去你妈妈那儿
Uh, I'm gonna drive over to your mother's house.
我知道她出城了 所以 如果你在
I know that she's out of town. So if you are there,
请... 请不要离开 好吗?
just... just don't go anywhere, okay?
不管我做了什么 我... 很抱歉
Whatever I did, I'm... I'm sorry.
David啊?
David?
嗯 这条是给David Shephard的留言
Uh, yes, this message is for David Shephard.
嗨 David
Hi, David.
我是Williams音乐学校的Summerland博士
This is Dr. Summerland from the Williams Conservatory.
请回电以确认时间
Just calling to confirm your slot.
下星期五 24号 晚上7点
Next Friday the 24th at 7:00 p.m.
我们希望见到你 祝好运
We look forward to seeing you, and good luck.
嘿 David 是爸爸
Hey, David. It's dad.
我 呃...
I'm, uh...
我在澳大利亚悉尼
I'm in Sydney, Australia.
有些事...
Something...
发生了一些事 我...
Something happened, and I...
我只想听听你的声音
I just needed to hear your voice.
呃 我待会儿再打来吧
Um, I guess I'll try you again later.
我爱你
I love you.
哥们儿 这太炫了
This is cool, dude.
像桥段一样
Very old school.
什么?
What?
就是 你和我...
You know, you and me...
穿越丛林...
Trekking through the jungle...
去做一些我们不清楚的事情
On our way to do something that we don't quite understand.
多好啊
Good times.
你介意我问你些事情吗?
You mind if I ask you somethin'?
问吧
Sure.
你为什么回来?
Why'd you come back?
你知道的... 就是回到岛上而已
You know... To the island.
你为什么回来?
Why'd you come back?
在洛杉矶的时候
Back in L.A.,
Jacob跳上我出租车的后座
Jacob hopped into the back of my cab,
告诉我 我应该回来 所以我就来了
and told me I was supposed to, so I came.
怎么?
What?
哥们儿 你要是有更好的理由回来 就说出来
If you have a better reason for coming back, let's hear it, man.
我回来 是因为我太伤心了
I came back here because I was broken.
我居然傻到 相信这个地方能慰藉我
And I was stupid enough to think this place would fix me.
哥们儿 抱歉
Dude, I'm sorry.
Hurley 我们还要走多远?
How much further we got, Hurley?
不远了 就快到了
It's not far. It's not far at all.
就在那儿
It's right there.
是个灯塔
It's a lighthouse.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我们之前怎么没见过?
How is it that we've never seen it before?
我猜 是我们没去找吧
I guess we weren't looking for it.
告诉我 我儿子在哪儿
So tell me where my son is.
我不知道你儿子在哪儿
I don't know where your son is.
别替他们说话了
Stop covering for them.
他们不会帮你了
They're not gonna help you anymore.
你要做的 就是告诉我真相
All you've gotta do is just tell me the truth.
我说的就是真相 听着 我们没抓你儿子
I am telling you the truth. Look, we don't have your kid.
- 我们从来没抓过你儿子!  - 别说谎了!
- We never had your kid!  - Stop lying to me!
你们拉我去寺庙 还折磨我
Your people took me to the temple and tortured me.
不是 我们抓你 是因为你在丛林里
No, we captured you because you were out here in the jungle
杀我们的人
picking our people off.
Claire 等等!
Claire, wait!
等等
Hold on.
"等"?
"Hold on"?
Jin 他们拿针扎我! 他们拿烙铁烫我!
Jin, they stuck me with needles! They branded me!
要不是我从寺庙里逃出来
And if I hadn't been able to escape from the temple,
他们就把我杀了
they would've killed me.
不 你记错了
No, you're not remembering things right.
噢 闭嘴 行吗?!
Oh, shut up, okay?!
再给你一次机会 再多给你一次机会
You've got one more chance. One more chance.
告诉我 我儿子在哪儿
Just tell me where my son is.
我不知道你那该死的孩子在哪儿!
I don't know where your damn kid is!
Kate带走了他!
Kate took him!
Kate带走了Aaron
Kate took Aaron.
她带着他离开了小岛
She took him with her when she left the island.
什么叫她带着他?
What do you mean she took him?
他一直跟... Kate在一起...
He's been with h... with Kate...
从三年前起就是这样
for the past three years.
Aaron三岁了
Aaron is 3.
他说的是真的
He's telling you the truth.
我们什么也没干
We had nothing to do with this.
所以你要是放了我
So if you just untie me,
我马上就走
I'll leave,
我发誓 我永远都不会告诉其他人
and I promise I will never tell anyone
我见过你
I ever even saw you.
放了我吧
Just untie me.
帅吧?
Pretty cool, huh?
Jacob在这儿?
Jacob's in here?
应该吧
I guess so.
但是我们要先上楼 把它打开
But first we gotta go upstairs and turn this thing on.
你胳膊上没说
It doesn't say anything on your arm
- 门会被锁上?  - 没
- about the door being jammed?  - No.
你先走
After you.
是你儿子吗?
Is that your son?
是的
Yes.
他真的很棒
He's really good.
他们这么小 不该承受这种压力
They are too young to have this kind of pressure,
对吗?
aren't they?
嗯 是的 他们确实太小了
Yes. Yes, they are.
站这儿看着 却没法帮忙 真难受
It's hard to watch and be unable to help.
你的儿子很有天赋
Your son has a gift.
他弹了多长时间?
How long has he been playing?
我...
I...
我不知道
I don't know.
哇
Whoa.
哥们儿 这太酷了
Dude, this is cool.
建这个 肯定是想帮船开过来之类的
Must've built this to help ships get here and stuff.
我猜他们用镜子 是因为...
I guess they used a mirror 'cause...
还没发明电呢
electricity hadn't been invented yet.
- Jacob在哪儿?  - 哦 他还没来呢
- Where's Jacob?  - Uh, he's not here yet.
我们开始吧
Let's get started.
到了108度的时候告诉我
Tell me when it gets to 108 degrees.
停
Stop.
你看到了吗?
Did you see that?
我看见什么了?
Did I see what?
镜子 我看见镜子里有东西
The mirror. I saw something in the mirror.
哥们儿 大海而已
It's just ocean, dude.
这上面刻了一堆名字
There are names.
转到23度
Turn it to 23 degrees.
噢 我... 我觉得Jacob不想...
Oh, I... I don't think Jacob wants...
啊? 这是什么?
What? What is that?
我的房子
It's my house.
我在那房子里长大的
It's the house I grew up in.
呃
Huh.
太诡异了
That's weird.
我在那儿从小住到大
I have lived in that house since I was a kid.
他一直在观察我们
He's been watching us.
每时每刻 我们所有人 他一直在观察我们
The whole time, all of us. He's been watching us.
Hurley啊
Hurley.
Jacob在哪儿?
Where's Jacob?
我不知道
I don't know.
你说过他会来这儿的
You said that he would be here.
我也只是... 猜猜而已
Well, I was just... kind of assuming.
Hurley啊...
Hurley...
我想知道 他干嘛要观察我
I wanna know why was he watching me.
我想知道 你赶快叫他出来啊
I wanna know, so you're gonna ask him right now.
这样没用 我跟你说过的
It doesn't work like that. I told you.
只有他想出现的时候 他才会出现
He just kinda shows up whenever he feels like it.
你要干嘛?
What are you doing?
- 他干嘛要观察我?  - 我不知道
- Why was he watching me?  - I don't know.
- 为什么我的名字 会写在这上面?  - 他没告诉我
- Why is my name written down on this thing?  - He didn't tell me.
他想从我这儿得到什么? 他想从我这儿得到什么?!
What does he want from me? What does he want from me?!
- 我本来要去...  - 我不知道 Jack!
- I was supposed to do...  - I don't know, Jack!
不要啊!
Don't!
表现得不错啊
You were great in there.
你看到我了?
You saw me?
我漏弹了几个音符
I missed a couple of notes.
我站那儿听的时候 觉得很棒
It sounded perfect from where I was standing.
David 你吓到我了
David, you scared the hell out of me.
那会儿你在奶奶家
You were at grandma's.
我以为 我能在你回家之前 赶回来的
I thought I could get back to your place before you got home.
我甚至不知道 你还在弹钢琴
I didn't even know you were still playing.
我答应过妈妈不告诉你的
I made mom promise not to tell you.
为什么?
Why?
你一直很看重这件事
It was always such a big deal to you.
你一直坐着看我练习
You used to sit and watch me practice.
你是那么...
You were so...
沉醉
into it.
我没有告诉你我来这儿 是因为...
I didn't tell you I was coming here because...
我不想让你看到 我失败的样子
I didn't want you to see me fail.
当我和你一样大的时候
You know, when I was your age,
我父亲也不想看到我失败
my father didn't want to see me fail either.
他常对我说...
He used to say to me that...
他说我没有天赋
He said that I didn't have what it takes.
这句话一直在我脑海中徜徉
I spent my whole life carrying that around with me.
我不想让你重蹈覆辙
And I don't ever want you to feel that way.
我一直深爱着你
I will always love you,
无论你做得怎么样
No matter what you do.
在... 在我看来 你一定不会失败的
In... in my eyes, you can never fail.
我只是想 成为你生命中的一部分
I just wanna be a part of your life.
好吧
Okay.
我买了点披萨在家里 你饿了吗?
I've got some pizza back at the house. You hungry?
当然
Sure.
好的
Good.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
怎么样了?
How'd it go?
伙计 你刚刚在哪儿啊?
Where were you, man?
无所谓啦 他反正又看不到我
Doesn't matter. He wouldn't have been able to see me anyway.
没错 如果你告诉了我
Yeah, well, I'd you had told me that
比如说 你解释了这一切的话
and had, like, explained everything,
或许Jack不会生气的
then maybe Jack wouldn't have freaked out
也不会把你的镜子砸得粉碎
and smashed your mirror into a billion pieces.
多亏了这七年多的霉运啊
Thanks for the seven years of bad luck, by the way.
你额头上有墨水
You got ink on your forehead.
我额头上有墨水? 你就只会说这个啊?!
I have ink on my forehead? That's all you have to say?!
Jack毁了你的灯塔 哥们!
Jack broke your lighthouse, dude!
任务失败了
Mission unaccomplished.
那些你说我们要去帮助的 来这个岛的人
Whoever you said we needed to help get to the island
- 全都没戏了  - 哦 我想他们会有办法的
- is totally screwed.  - Oh, I'm sure they'll find some other way.
那么...
So...
你让我做的每一件事 都被搞砸了
Everything you wanted me to do didn't get done,
你... 一点儿也不介意?
and... you don't even care?
等一下
Wait a minute.
你就是想让Jack 看到镜子里的东西吧?
Did you want Jack to see what was in that mirror?
为什么?
Why?
只有这样 才能让他意识到 他自己有多么重要
It was the only way for him to understand how important he is.
如果这是你的计划 那就事与愿违了
Well, if that was your plan, I think it backfired, man.
Jack来这儿 是因为他有事要做
Jack is here because he has to do something.
别人不能告诉他是什么 他得自己发现
He can't be told what that is. He's gotta find it himself.
有时候 你可以搭上一辆出租车
Sometimes you can just hop in the back of someone's cab
然后告诉他们去哪儿
and tell 'em what they're supposed to do.
但有时
Other times,
你得让他们自己 面朝大海想想
You have to let him look out at the ocean for a while.
下次 你还是先把一切告诉我 好不?
Well, next time, how about you tell me everything up front?
我不喜欢玩神秘这一套 懂吗?
I'm not big on secret plans, okay?
我可禁不起你不来的后果 Hugo啊
I couldn't risk you not coming, Hugo.
我得确保把你和Jack一起
I had to get you and Jack
- 从神庙那儿叫过来  - 什么? 为什么?
- as far away from that temple as I possibly could.  - What? Why?
因为有人马上就要去那儿了
'Cause someone's coming there.
很坏的人
Someone bad.
兄弟 我们得去警告下他们
Dude, we have to warn them.
你不能警告他们 Hugo
You can't warn them, Hugo.
对不起 太迟了
I'm sorry. It's too late.
听着 如果我不杀他 他会杀了我
Look, if I didn't kill him, he would've killed me.
真高兴你没替他松绑
I'm glad you didn't untie him.
Claire 不管你是怎么想的...
Claire, please, whatever you're thinking...
为什么你会说Kate在抚养Aaron?
Why'd you say that Kate was raising Aaron?
我骗你的
I was lying.
为什么?
Why?
因为我想保住他的命
Because I wanted to save his life.
但你是对的
But you were right.
The Others带走了你的孩子
The Others have your baby.
Aaron在寺庙里
Aaron is at the temple.
我看到他在那儿了
I know because I saw him there.
但你需要我的帮助 才能找到他
But you'll need me to get to him.
我们怎么进去?
How do we get in?
有条秘道 没人会发现我们
There's a secret way. No one will see us.
谢谢 Jin 谢谢
Thank you, Jin. Thank you.
真高兴你是在说谎
And I'm so glad to know you were lying.
如果你说的是真的话
Because if what you said was the truth,
如果Kate在抚养Aaron的话?
if Kate was raising Aaron?
我会杀了她
I'd kill her.
打扰你们了吗?
Am I interrupting?
是John?
John?
不是John啦 这是我的朋友
That's not John. This is my friend.